[{
  "id": 1,
  "question": "Danish brothers Lars and Jens Rasmussen developed a platform in their start-up company Where 2, which after being taken over by an internet giant became what?",
  "answer": "Google Maps",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 2,
  "question": "How many countries are larger than Australia?",
  "answer": "5",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 3,
  "question": "In what city did the Commonwealth Parliament first sit?",
  "answer": "Melbourne",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 4,
  "question": "How many states and territories in total are there in Australia?",
  "answer": "8",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 5,
  "question": "Which is the largest Australian State in terms of area?(Abrreviation)",
  "answer": "WA",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 6,
  "question": "Which food product rich in vitamin B did Cyril Callister develop?",
  "answer": "Vegemite",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 7,
  "question": "Who was the first Australian to have a No. 1 international hit song, with a version of \"A Pub with No Beer\"?",
  "answer": "Slim Dusty",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 8,
  "question": "Which venue has hosted the Australian Open since 1988?",
  "answer": "Melbourne Park",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 9,
  "question": "Actress born in 1967 whose first film was Bush Christmas but came to prominence in the film Dead Calm.",
  "answer": "Nicole Kidman",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 10,
  "question": "Hugh Jackman was born in which city?",
  "answer": "Sydney",
  "level": "Easy"
}, {
  "id": 11,
  "question": "In what year was Advance Australia Fair proclaimed as the national anthem by the Governor-General?",
  "answer": "1984",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 12,
  "question": "What Australian company is the largest surfwear manufacturer?",
  "answer": "Quicksilver",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 13,
  "question": "How many gold medals did Australians win at the 2002 Winter Olympic Games?",
  "answer": "2",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 14,
  "question": "Which is the second largest city in NSW?",
  "answer": "Newcastle",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 15,
  "question": "How much of Australia is classified as desert in percentage?",
  "answer": "35",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 16,
  "question": "What animal is on the right of the Australian Commonwealth Coat of Arms?",
  "answer": "Emu",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 17,
  "question": "How many ships were in the First Fleet?",
  "answer": "11",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 18,
  "question": "Who was Australia's longest serving Prime Minister?",
  "answer": "Robert Menzies",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 19,
  "question": "In what year was gold first discovered in Victoria and NSW to begin the “Gold Rush”?",
  "answer": "1851",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 20,
  "question": "The Australian Senate has how many members?",
  "answer": "76",
  "level": "Medium"
}, {
  "id": 21,
  "question": "Cate Blanchett has received an Academy Award nomination for what movie?",
  "answer": "Elizabeth",
  "level": "Hard"
}, {
  "id": 22,
  "question": "What is Kylie Minogue’s lingerie line called?",
  "answer": "Love Kylie",
  "level": "Hard"
}, {
  "id": 23,
  "question": "In what year did Captain Arthur Phillip and the First Fleet arrive at Botany Bay?",
  "answer": "1788",
  "level": "Hard"
}, {
  "id": 24,
  "question": "In what year was decimal currency introduced?",
  "answer": "1966",
  "level": "Hard"
}, {
  "id": 25,
  "question": "Who designed the Sydney Opera House?",
  "answer": "Joern Utzon",
  "level": "Hard"
}, {
  "id": 26,
  "question": "Name Australia’s western-most point?",
  "answer": "Steep Point",
  "level": "Hard"
}, {
  "id": 27,
  "question": "What creature does Jana Pittman have tattooed on her body?",
  "answer": "Bee",
  "level": "Hard"
}, {
  "id": 28,
  "question": "Who became Olympic champion for the women's 400 metres at the 2000 Summer Olympics?",
  "answer": "Cathy Freeman",
  "level": "Hard"
}, {
  "id": 29,
  "question": "Bon Scott became the lead singer of which band from 1974 until his death in 1980?",
  "answer": "AC/DC",
  "level": ""
}, {
  "id": 30,
  "question": "2017 was a great year for Ed Sheeran, how many singles did he have in the top 10 best selling singles of the year?",
  "answer": "4",
  "level": "Hard"
}]